<resources>
    <string name="HSE_Drug_Service">HSE Drug Service\n<u>091-561299</u></string>
    <string name="Samaritans">Samaritans\n<u>1850-609090</u></string>
    <string name="HSE_Drug_Helpline">HSE Drugs Helpline\n<u>1800-459459</u></string>
    <string name="Samaritans1">Samaritans\n<u>091-561222</u></string>

    <string name="app_name">Galway Safe</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>

    <string name="parse_app_id">YOUR_APPLICATION_ID</string>
    <string name="parse_client_key">YOUR_CLIENT_KEY</string>

    <string name="SMS_ICEcontact">Hi, I have requested you to be one of my ICE contacts. If I feel that I really need to talk to someone after a night out in Galway I have asked if you would be willing to help. It would be great if you could have a conversation with X about keeping safe in Galway and download the app:\n https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.girtmobile.galwaysafe </string>
    <string name="SMS_Alert">I really need to talk to someone now. Can you please contact me immediately? This message has been delivered by the Galway Safe app.</string>
    <string name="SMS_Leave">Hi, I am leaving the risk area now! This message has been delivered by the Galway Safe app.</string>


    <string name="ice_explanation">When you save the ICE Contacts the app will send an SMS informing them that they have been selected as your ICE Contact.\n ICE Contacts do not need to have the app installed. </string>


    <string name="terms">1. Introduction \n\n1.1 These terms and conditions shall govern your use of galwaysafeapp (hereon referred to as ‘app’). \n1.2 By using our app, you accept these terms and conditions in full; accordingly, if you disagree with these terms and conditions or any part of these terms and conditions, you must not use our app. \n1.3 If you register with our app, we will ask you to expressly agree to these terms and conditions. \n1.4 You must be at least 18 years of age to use our app; by using our app or agreeing to these terms and conditions, you warrant and represent to us that you are at least 18 years of age. \n1.5 The app utilizes ‘whatsapp’. Any use of the app will also be bound by the terms and conditions of whatsapp.  </string>
    <string name="terms2">\n2. Credit \n\n2.1 This document was created using a template from SEQ Legal (http://www.seqlegal.com).</string>
    <string name="terms3">\n3. Copyright notice \n\n3.1 Copyright (c) 2017. Western Region Drug and Alcohol Task Force ltd. (hereon referred to as WRDATF). \n3.2 Subject to the express provisions of these terms and conditions: (a) we, together with our licensors, own and control all the copyright and other intellectual property rights in our app and the material on our app; and (b) all the copyright and other intellectual property rights in our app and the material on our website are reserved. (c) data pertaining to an individual user may be obtained  by the individual user or by a nominated (i.e. an ‘In case of emergency (ICE) contact’) when the ICE contact has been notified by the app concerning an individual user.</string>
    <string name="terms4">\n4. Licence to use website \n\n4.1 You may: (a) view pages from our app in a web browser; (b) download pages from our app for caching in a web browser; (c) print pages from our app; (subject to the other provisions of these terms and conditions.) \n4.2 Except as expressly permitted by Section 4.1 or the other provisions of these terms and conditions, you must not download any material from our app or save any such material to your computer. \n4.3 You may only use our app for your own personal purposes, and you must not use our app for any other purposes. \n4.4 Except as expressly permitted by these terms and conditions, you must not edit or otherwise modify any material on our app. \n4.5 Unless you own or control the relevant rights in the material, you must not: (a) republish material from our app (including republication on another website or app); (b) sell, rent or sub-license material from our app; (c) show any material from our app in public; (d) exploit material from our app for a commercial purpose; or (e) redistribute material from our app. \n4.7 We reserve the right to restrict access to areas of our app, or indeed our whole app, at our discretion; you must not circumvent or bypass, or attempt to circumvent or bypass, any access restriction measures on our app.</string>
    <string name="terms5">\n5. Acceptable use \n\n5.1 You must not: (a) use our app in any way or take any action that causes, or may cause, damage to the app or impairment of the performance, availability or accessibility of the app; (b) use our app in any way that is unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful, or in connection with any unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful purpose or activity; (c) use our app to copy, store, host, transmit, send, use, publish or distribute any material which consists of (or is linked to) any spyware, computer virus, Trojan horse, worm, keystroke logger, rootkit or other malicious computer software; (d) conduct any systematic or automated data collection activities (including without limitation scraping, data mining, data extraction and data harvesting) on or in relation to our app without our express written consent (e) access or otherwise interact with our app using any robot, spider or other automated means. \n5.2 You must not use data collected from our app to contact individuals, companies or other persons or entities. \n5.3 You must ensure that all the information you supply to us through our app, or in relation to our app, is true, accurate, current, complete and non-misleading. </string>
    <string name="terms6">\n6. Registration and accounts \n\n6.1 To be eligible for an account on our app under this Section 6, you must be resident or situated in the Republic of Ireland. \n6.2 You may register for an account with our app by completing and submitting the account registration form on our app. \n6.3 You must not allow any other person to use your account to access the app. \n6.4 You must notify us in writing immediately if you become aware of any unauthorised use of your account. \n6.5 You must not use any other person\'s account to access the app, unless you have that person\'s express permission to do so.</string>
    <string name="terms7">\n7. User login details \n\n7.1 If you register for an account with our app. \n7.2 Your user ID must not be liable to mislead and must comply; you must not use your account or user ID for or in connection with the impersonation of any person. \n7.3 You must keep your password confidential. \n7.4 You must notify us in writing immediately if you become aware of any disclosure of your password. \n7.5 You are responsible for any activity on our app arising out of any failure to keep your password confidential, and may be held liable for any losses arising out of such a failure. \n7.6 Cancellation and suspension of account. We may: (a) suspend your account; (b) cancel your account; and/or (c) edit your account details,  at any time in our sole discretion without notice or explanation. You may cancel your account on our app.</string>
    <string name="terms8">\n8. Limited warranties \n\n8.1 We do not warrant or represent: (a) the completeness or accuracy of the information published on our app; (b) that the material on the app is up to date; or (c) that the app or any service on the website will remain available. \n8.2 We reserve the right to discontinue or alter any or all of our app services, and to stop publishing our app, at any time in our sole discretion without notice or explanation; and save to the extent expressly provided otherwise in these terms and conditions, you will not be entitled to any compensation or other payment upon the discontinuance or alteration of any app services, or if we stop publishing the app. \n8.3 To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law and subject to Section 9.1, we exclude all representations and warranties relating to the subject matter of these terms and conditions, our app and the use of our app.</string>
    <string name="terms9">\n9. Limitations and exclusions of liability \n\n9.1 Nothing in these terms and conditions will: (a) limit or exclude any liability for death or personal injury resulting from negligence; (b) limit or exclude any liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation; (c) limit any liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or (d) exclude any liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law. \n9.2 The limitations and exclusions of liability set out in this Section 9 and elsewhere in these terms and conditions: (a) are subject to Section 9.1; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under these terms and conditions or relating to the subject matter of these terms and conditions, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort (including negligence) and for breach of statutory duty, except to the extent expressly provided otherwise in these terms and conditions. \n9.3 To the extent that our app and the information and services on our app are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature. \n9.4 We will not be liable to you in respect of any losses arising out of any event or events beyond our reasonable control. \n9.5 We will not be liable to you in respect of any business losses, including (without limitation) loss of or damage to profits, income, revenue, use, production, anticipated savings, business, contracts, commercial opportunities or goodwill. \n9.6 We will not be liable to you in respect of any loss or corruption of any data, database or software. \n9.7 We will not be liable to you in respect of any special, indirect or consequential loss or damage. \n9.8 You accept that we have an interest in limiting the personal liability of our officers and employees and, having regard to that interest, you acknowledge that we are a limited liability entity; you agree that you will not bring any claim personally against our officers or employees in respect of any losses you suffer in connection with the app or these terms and conditions (this will not, of course, limit or exclude the liability of the limited liability entity itself for the acts and omissions of our officers and employees). </string>
    <string name="terms10">\n10. Breaches of these terms and conditions \n\n10.1 Without prejudice to our other rights under these terms and conditions, if you breach these terms and conditions in any way, or if we reasonably suspect that you have breached these terms and conditions in any way, we may: (a) send you one or more formal warnings; (b) temporarily suspend your access to our app; (c) permanently prohibit you from accessing our app; (d) commence legal action against you, whether for breach of contract or otherwise; and/or (e) suspend or delete your account on our app.  \n10.2 Where we suspend or prohibit or block your access to our app or a part of our app, you must not take any action to circumvent such suspension or prohibition or blocking. </string>
    <string name="terms11">\n11. Variation \n\n11.1 We may revise these terms and conditions from time to time. \n11.2 The revised terms and conditions shall apply to the use of our website from the date of publication of the revised terms and conditions on the website, and you hereby waive any right you may otherwise have to be notified of, or to consent to, revisions of these terms and conditions. \n11.3 If you have given your express agreement to these terms and conditions, we will ask for your express agreement to any revision of these terms and conditions; and if you do not give your express agreement to the revised terms and conditions within such period as we may specify, we will disable or delete your account on the website, and you must stop using the website.</string>
    <string name="terms12">\n12. Assignment \n\n12.1 You hereby agree that we may assign, transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with our rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions. \n12.2 You may not without our prior written consent assign, transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with any of your rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="terms13">\n13. Severability \n\n13.1 If a provision of these terms and conditions is determined by any court or other competent authority to be unlawful and/or unenforceable, the other provisions will continue in effect. \n13.2 If any unlawful and/or unenforceable provision of these terms and conditions would be lawful or enforceable if part of it were deleted, that part will be deemed to be deleted, and the rest of the provision will continue in effect.</string>
    <string name="terms14">\n14. Third party rights \n\n14.1 A contract under these terms and conditions is for our benefit and your benefit, and is not intended to benefit or be enforceable by any third party. \n14.2 The exercise of the parties\' rights under a contract under these terms and conditions is not subject to the consent of any third party.</string>
    <string name="terms15">\n15. Entire agreement \n\n15.1 Subject to Section 9.1, these terms and conditions, together with our privacy policy, shall constitute the entire agreement between you and us in relation to your use of our website and shall supersede all previous agreements between you and us in relation to your use of our website.</string>
    <string name="terms16">\n16. Law and jurisdiction \n\n16.1 These terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with Irish law. \n16.2 Any disputes relating to these terms and conditions shall be subject to the exclusive OR jurisdiction of the courts of the Republic of Ireland.</string>
    <string name="terms17">\n17. Our details \n\n17.1 This app is owned and operated by WRDATF. \n17.2 We are registered in the Republic of Ireland as a charity under registration number : CHY 18126, and our registered office is at Western Region Drugs and Alcohol Task Force Unit 6, Galway Technology Park, Parkmore, Galway. \n17.3 Our principal place of business is at  Unit 6, Galway Technology Park, Parkmore, Galway. \n17.4 You can contact us: (a) by post, using the postal address given above (b) by telephone, published on our website (d) by email, using the email address published on our website. \n17.5  We are registered as the Western Region Drug and Alcohol Task Force ltd. with the Charity Regulation Authority (number : 20068882) are subject to the rules of the authority, which can be found at http:\/\/www.charitiesregulatoryauthority.ie/</string>
</resources>